>> Jem Young:  我们在安全性方面有很长的会话，但  是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: HTTPS, we had a long
session on security, but what is HTTPS?
为何我们要这样做呢 ?
Why do we need it?
我们触及了一点点。
We touched on it a little bit.
萨姆?
Sam?
>> 演讲者 2: 基于  的 SSL 覆盖或安全套接字层。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's SSL over, or
secure sockets layer, over HTTPS.
>> Jem Young: 完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Exactly.
>> 扬声器 2: 通过 HTTP。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Over HTTP.
>> Jem Young: 为什么我们需要它 ?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And why we need it though?
>> 演讲者 2: 那么任何人和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So that anybody and
他们的狗不能检查你和服务器之间的交通吗
their dog can't inspect the traffic
between you and the server?
>> Jem Young: 这就是正确的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: That's exactly right.
认为在没有那么长的时间里
It's kind of wild to think that in
the olden days of not that long
我真的可以装个假路由器
ago I literally could just
set up a fake router or
我可以窃听你的电话
I could just tap into your phone line and
拦截所有即将发生的数据并且完全未加密。
intercept all of the data that's coming
and going and it was totally unencrypted.
这相当于我在房间里大喊大叫，我的数据是什么。
It's the equivalent of me yelling
across the room, what my data is.
如果有人碰巧在这附近
And if someone just happens
to be in earshot of that,
他们知道我在做什么
they know exactly what I'm doing.
这就是互联网过去工作的方式。
And this is the way
the Internet used to work.
幸运的是，由于许多科技公司的持续存在，
Fortunately now, thanks to persistence
of a lot of the tech companies and
主要是浏览器，我们现在都使用  。
mainly browsers, we all use HTTPS now.
而这又是另一件事
And that's one of the things that, again,
互联网一直以它的方式运作是很有趣的。
it's fascinating that the Internet
keeps working the way it does.
我们不断推进这些新协议和标准
And we keep pushing these new
protocols and standards forward,
虽然没有一个实体说我们应该如何运作
even though there's no one entity
that saying how we should operate.
但是  它所做的是对传输中的所有数据进行加密。
But HTTPS, what it does is it
encrypts all the data in transit.
在使用 HTTP 的旧天数和当前天数中，如果我要
In the old days and
current days with HTTP, if I was going to
frontendmasters.com 放我的信用卡信息，是纯文本的。
frontendmasters.com put in my credit
card information, it'd be in plain text.
我可以拦截那包然后读
I could just intercept that packet and
read it.
我甚至可以把它传递给主宰者，这样他们就不会
And I can even pass it along back to
frontendmasters, so that they wouldn't
你甚至都不知道你的数据被偷了
even know or you wouldn't even know that
your data is being sniffed and stolen.
事实上，他们可以一直这样做，而人们也这样做。
In fact, they can keep doing that for
years and people did that.
人们就像是在我使用这个网站的时候
And people were like,
why is it when I use this website,
一个月后我的信用卡被盗了吗
about a month later my credit
card gets stolen mysteriously?
这是因为人们坐在中间，拦截请求。
And it's because people were sitting in
the middle and intercepting requests.
那些可能是最邪恶的袭击者
And those are probably the most
nefarious kinds of attackers,
那些不允许你知道他们在做什么的人
the ones that don't let you know
that they're doing anything.
你只会觉得这里发生的事情是错误的
You just sort of start the seeing
things go wrong here in there.
但现在那是 HTTP 的另一个好处
But now so what it use to be
another benefit of HTTP was,
或者 HTTP 的下侧是你不能保证你在跟谁说话
or a down side of HTTP was you couldn't
guarantee who you were talking to.
比如说我们之前说过我的域到期了吗，
For instance, we talked earlier
about if I let my domain expire and
有人能很快地把它捡起来
someone picks it up really
quickly which they tend to do.
我现在可以创建 jemyoung.com 或者 frontendmasters.com
I can now create jemyoung.com or
frontendmasters.com if let it drop and
你没有证据证明这不是你之前跟你说话的人
you have no proof that this isn't
the person you were talking to before.
因为大多数人没有，你不检查 IP 地址。
Because most people don't,
you're not checking IP addresses.
大多数人永远不会检出 IP 地址。
Most people are never gonna
check out IP addresses.
你只会检查那个域名
You're just gonna check that domain name.
我认为互联网曾经是这样的，这真的很有趣。
And I think it's really interesting
that the Internet used to be like this.
你以前能做这些事
You used to be able to
do all these things.
如果谷歌让它的域名到期了，我就可以，就像我现在是谷歌。
If Google let its domain expire,
I can just be, like, I'm now Google.
好的请登录
Yeah, go ahead and log in.
你不能登录吗
You can't log in?
那就继续努力吧
Wow, just keep trying.
继续输入您的所有凭证。
Keep entering all your credentials.
我们会说，互联网坏了，或者类似的东西。
And we'd just say, the Internet's
broken or something like that.
因为我在 google.com 上很清楚，也没有办法来验证。
Because I'm clearly on google.com and
there's no way of verifying that.
但是  不仅加密传输内容，它说，嘿，你是
But HTTPS not only encrypts things in
transport, it says, hey, the person you're
保证你跟他们说话我们保证
talking to is guaranteed that you're
talking to them and we guarantee it.
现在谁来保证呢
Now who guarantees that?
这叫认证机构
It's something called
certificate authorities.
同样，因特网建立在信任和认证中心的基础之上
Again, the Internet is built on trust and
certificate authorities are trusted
证明你是谁的权威
authorities that validate
you are who you say you are.
到目前为止还有什么问题吗
Does that any questions on that so far?
我们会继续做
Cuz we're gonna keep going on HTTPS.
有人震惊了互联网过去的这种方式
Is anybody shocked that the Internet
used to be this way and
现在好点了吗
now it's getting better?
我想如果下一代会说，等等，互联网就像这样。
And I think if the next generation will
say, wait, the Internet was like this.
那是，哇，
That was, wow,
就像人们把枪从左到右
it was just like the wild west of
people shooting guns left and right.
我也会很喜欢的
And I'll be like, yeah, pretty much.
那天一切都不一样了
It was anything goes back in the day.
幸运的是，通过  你不能嗅到这种流量。
Fortunately now, with HTTPS,
you can't sniff that traffic.
它在客户端上加密，在服务器上解密。
It's encrypted on the clients and
decrypted on the server.
这又是公用密钥认证。
So it's that public key
authentication again.
不是 SSH ，而是在客户有钥匙的情况下
It's not SSH, but think of it similarly
where the client has a key and
它从服务器获取的证书。
a certificate that it
gets from the server.
所以我第一次联系 frontendmasters.com 他们说，好的，
So the first time I connect
the frontendmasters.com, they say, okay,
你从没来过这里
you've never been here before.
这是我的公用证书验证我是谁
Here's my public certificate
verifying who I am.
这就是如何加密所有数据的方法。
And here's how to encrypt all that data.
因此，我使用该公用证书对所有数据进行加密，并且
So I use that public certificate
to encrypt all the data, and
那我就把它传下来 frontendmasters.com 或者你的服务器，
then I send it down the
frontendmasters.com or your server, and
这两者之间的任何东西都只是些 " jiberish"
anything between is just jibberish.
这只是加密数据
It's just encrypted data.
唯一能解密它的人是 Fronend Masters ，因为他们认为
The only one who can decrypt it is
Frontend Masters because they hold that
专用密钥。
private key.
您的服务器拥有专用密钥。
And your server holds a private key.
所以没有人能对它进行加密
So no one in between can encrypt it.
很有趣这让我很怀疑政府
Funny enough, and this makes me
really suspicious of the government,
它们不是针对 的。
they were not against HTTPS.
一般来说，加密的时候，政府是反对一切的，
Generally, when it comes to encryption,
the government is against all of it,
因为他们不能再看你的数据了
because they can't read your data anymore,
but
他们没有用 的牛肉
they don't really have beef with HTTPS.
这让我很怀疑那是个正切的
Which makes me really suspicious,
that's totally a tangent and
与此无关。
not related to this course.
但现在的情况是
But, what happens is now,
如果你像我有  那么一切都很安全
if you're like I have HTTPS everything's
secure everything's hunky dory.
我们很好我们再也不用担心安全了
We're good, we're never have
to worry about security again.
这都取决于这些认证中心。
This all depends on those
certificate authorities.
所以如果我登记我的域名，我说，嘿，安全认证中心，
So if when I registered my domain, I say,
hey Mrs. security certificate authority,
我是杰姆 - 扬我要注册网址 jemyoung.com
I'm Jem Young and
I'm going to register jemyoung.com.
他们就像，我们怎么知道你是谁 ?
They're like, how do we know
you are who you say you are?
你会经历一系列的认证步骤你就喜欢
And you go through a series of
authentication steps and you're like,
好吧这个人是值得信赖的
okay, yeah,
this this person is trustworthy.
我们要把我们的邮票放在它的验证上
We're gonna put our stamp
on it that verifies it.
如果我们去找我们的浏览器
And if we go to our browser,
我们可以去查证书局
we can actually check out
the certificate authorities.
我们试试一个随机的网站
Let's try, what's a random website,
我们说 Google，它很容易， Google.com。
let's say Google,
it's an easy one, Google.com.
我可以看这里，我说连接是安全的，我可以查看证书。
And I can look here, I say connection is
secure, I can look at the certificate.
我们可以更多地挖掘这一证书。
We can dig in that certificate a bit more.
>> Jem Young: 它有很多关于谁是权威的信息，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And it has a bunch of
information about who the authority is,
比如我们怎么知道这些人是谁
like how do we know these people
are who they say they are.
证书级别不同。
There are different
levels of certificates.
更贵的，在你看到的地方，这个网站是经过验证的
The more expensive ones where you see
the full, this site is verified by that
其实是 google.com 是比较贵的。
it's actually google.com,
are the more expensive ones.
这不是我们今天要执行的那种
That's not the kind we're
gonna implement today.
那些会花更多钱的我们会在第二次实施免费的
Those tend to cost a bit more money, we're
gonna implement a free one in a second,
应该挺有趣的
which should be pretty fun.
但它告诉你们关于加密数据的算法。
But it tells you all about the algorithm
that's encrypting that data.
有些人比其他人更安全
Some are more secure than others.
那么这是一个，是吗 ?
So here's a, yes?
>> 扬声器 2: 椭圆曲线公用密钥，以及
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's elliptic
curve public key, and
那是国安局已知的漏洞
that's the NSA has known vulnerabilities.
>> Jem Young: 据我们所知。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: As far as we know.
如果他们有的话他们会告诉我们吗
And if they did, would they tell us?
>> 扬声器 2: 否，他们已经- >> Jem Young: 他们已经证明了吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No, they've already-
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: They've proven it?
>> 演讲者 2: 这是众所周知的，这就是为什么政府对 SSL的渴望。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's known, that's why
the government hunky dory with SSL.
> > Jem Young: 是的，是的，我应该做一个关于密码术的章节。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, well, yeah,
man I should do a section on cryptography.
老实说我没资格谈密码术
Now I to be honest, I am not
qualified to talk about cryptography,
大多数人不是除非你是数学家
most people are not unless
you're a mathematician.
但是关于密码术之类的规矩
But the rule on cryptography and
things like that, don't roll your own,
你还不够聪明
you're not smart enough.
我不是指那是什么意思
[LAUGH] I don't mean that to be mean.
如果你自己卷下密码你会有麻烦的
If you roll your own crypto,
you're gonna be in trouble.
这就是为什么我们有这些已知的算法，只能用于 。
That's why we have these known algorithms
that you can only use for HTTPS.
你不能就这样我就能创造 Jem 的散列算法然后把它引出来
You can't just, I'm gonna create Jem's
hashing algorithm and then serve that out.
这不起作用 你得用一个已知的标准
That doesn't work.
You have to use a known standard that
大家都同意
everybody agrees on.
但是说到密码术和加密东西
But speaking of cryptography and
encrypting things,
使用这种方法的缺点是什么，而不是 256 位
what's the downside of using like,
instead of 256 bits for
键，例如使用 1024 或 248?
the key, say using 1024 or 248?
好的好的 >> 扬声器 3: 更多字节，更多数据，
Yes, here?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: More bytes, more data,
慢了
it's slower.
> > Jem Young: 是的，速度较慢。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, it's slower.
你在理论上更安全
You're theoretically more secure.
但是当我的数据超安全的时候会有一个递减的回报点
But there's a point of diminishing returns
where you're like my data is ultra secure,
但现在它需要更长的时间和所有这些东西随着时间的推移而增加。
but it now takes longer and
all these things add up over time.
这些都是微秒，纳秒，但是如果你用一个巨大的钥匙，
These are microseconds, nanoseconds, but
if you use a giant key and it hashes,
客户必须解密，服务器也必须解密。
the client has to decrypt that,
the server has to decrypt that too.
奇怪的事实，当我们把 Netflix 转换为  它花费了我们几百万
Weird facts, when we converted Netflix
over to HTTPS, it costs us a few million
计算时间的花费，因为解密和解密的所有密码
dollars in compute time, because all
that cryptography of decrypting and
加密，解密和加密，成本 CPU 时间。
encrypting, decrypting and
encrypting, that cost CPU time.
当你说的是数万亿的请求时，这会更快地增加。
And when you're talking about trillions
of requests, that adds up really quickly.
所以这就是为什么  真正地将它推出来的原因。
So that's why HTTPS was
really slow to roll it out.
今天成功推出的原因是
The reason why it has rolled
out successfully today is
因为浏览器制造了我们
because browsers made us.
他们开始羞辱那些不加密的人就像是
They started shaming people now where if
it's not encrypted there's like a big like
斜杠或锁定符号或类似的原因，因为它们希望
slash or the lock sign or
something like that because they want to
鼓励人们使用  因为它只是做事情的更好方式。
encourage people to use HTTPS because
it's just a better way of doing things.
其实你不能用服务工人网蓝牙，
In fact you can't use a service
workers web bluetooth,
Web 安全付款方式 ( 如无 ) 。
web secure payments things
like that without HTTPS.
这就像浏览器的一点点泥
And that's just like a little
nudge by the browsers,
如果要使用最新功能，那么最好升级系统。
hey if you want to use the latest
features, you better upgrade your system.